If it were you,
you would have saved me too.
You have so much confidence in me.
Wouldn't you save me?
Take a guess.
Gu Qingyu,
what are you doing?
You're awake.
How are you feeling? Any pain?
Should I call the doctor?
I'm fine.
I'm just
a bit thirsty.
Are
you okay?
Yesterday I...
I'm fine.
You saved me.
But that car...
The police have been here.
They said it was an accident
due to the slippery road,
and the driver was drunk
and lost control.
It was just an accident.
Yesterday,
I forgot to tell you,
happy birthday.
Look at you,
so busy you forgot your own birthday.
Isn't October 27th your birthday?
Tian.
Are you okay?
Are you feeling unwell?
Or are you scared?
[Gu Qingyu.]
[Guan Tian.]
[Who are you?]
Xintian,
[How many secrets are you hiding?]
What happened?
What's wrong? Was there a car accident?
I'm fine.
It was just a scare.
What would you do
if you discovered that something you've always believed in
is not what you thought it was?
What would you do?
Is it related to Lin Jiming
Or
it's related to the thing three years ago.
No matter what you find,
remember not to be impulsive.
What the law and justice need
is evidence,
not lynching.
Don't get yourself into trouble.
I know.
I just need some time.
You're useless!
You can't even handle this small matter,
and even let Jiming get hurt.
Are you too soft to do it?
No.
Jiming suddenly rushed out
and pushed her away.
Wu Zhanshan,
I think you're getting worse as you get older.
You...
Wen Shiyi,
he's my son.
He's my own son.
I saw him
being hit
by me.
He's still lying in the hospital.
How can I
meet him in the future?
How can I face him?
Your son?
Remember your identity.
He is Lin Jiming,
the future master of Lin Group.
You are just his driver.
Understand?
Mr. Lin,
do you need to be transferred?
No,
it's not a big deal.
Here are the documents you need to sign.
Bring me my pen.
Alright, take it back.
Contact me by phone if necessary.
Everything is going well at the company.
Please rest assured and focus on recovery.
Thank you, Guan Lu.
Actually,
I know it's not an accident.
That car
was heading for you, right?
Are you in trouble?
Tell me.
I can help you.
No.
It was just an accident.
Guan Tiantian,
I'm not stupid.
Your eyes are complicated every time you look at me.
Tell me.
Why are you
getting close to me?
Mr. Lin,
you just got hurt.
You need to rest more.
Don't overthink.
Isn't October 27th your birthday?
Yesterday.
I forgot to tell you.
Happy birthday.
I watched him grow up.
I'm Rh-negative.
I can do this.
Take mine.
Wen Shiyi.
Lin Jiming.
Who should I hate?
Who can I trust?
Why you?
[The truth]
[is like the moonlight,]
[which occasionally breaks through the clouds,]
[but cannot illuminate all the darkness.]
[And some choices,]
[once made,]
[can never be undone.]